[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How long is a day on the planet Mars?", "correct_answer": "24.6 Earth hours", "incorrect_answers": ["48 Earth hours", "26 Earth hours", "12.6 Earth hours"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which statement is not true about Madame LaForce, who was a Confederate spy during the American Civil War?", "correct_answer": "She was French born.", "incorrect_answers": ["She was a man.", "She was a flirt.", "She led the take-over of the steamer St. Nicholas in 1861."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What event did the terrorists target in the 1977 movie Black Sunday?", "correct_answer": "Super Bowl", "incorrect_answers": ["Democratic Convention", "Times Square Ball Drop", "Macys Thanksgiving Parade"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Once rice is soft enough, you should add this.", "correct_answer": "A tablespoon of butter", "incorrect_answers": ["A tablespoon of turmeric powder", "A tablespoon of ground nutmeg", "A tablespoon of hot pepper"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "According to one theory, the name of this US state comes from the French word for hurricane.", "correct_answer": "Oregon", "incorrect_answers": ["Arizona", "Colorado", "Vermont"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the 2003 movie Elf, Will Ferrell plays an oversized Elf whose name is what?", "correct_answer": "Buddy", "incorrect_answers": ["Benny", "Billy", "Bobby"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does the e.e. in the name, e.e. cummings stand for?", "correct_answer": "Edward Estlin", "incorrect_answers": ["Edar Eastwood", "Edward Elgar", "Edgar Edward"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Complete this Irish saying: The whole world cannot make a ________ out of a donkey.", "correct_answer": "race horse", "incorrect_answers": ["poet", "nobleman", "artist"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Chihuahuas are the only dogs to be born with what?", "correct_answer": "An incomplete skull", "incorrect_answers": ["An extra leg tendon", "Hairless inner ears", "Two extra canine teeth"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what novel does Charles Dickens depict Mr. Thomas Gradgrind, the teacher who teaches his students nothing but facts?", "correct_answer": "Hard Times", "incorrect_answers": ["Dombey and Son", "Bleak House", "Great Expectations"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What other character, besides Leonard, claims to be suffering from anterograde amnesia in Memento?", "correct_answer": "Sammy Jankis", "incorrect_answers": ["Natalie", "Teddy Gammell", "Burt"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the nature of the so-called Socratic Method of inquiry?", "correct_answer": "Answering a question with another question", "incorrect_answers": ["Asking the same question many times by rephrasing it", "Answering a foolish question with a more foolish answer", "Asking very personal questions to embarrass the other party"]}]